视觉感一直让人着迷。
The sense of vision has long fascinated human kind.
在希腊人的时代，他们认为视觉有点类似于感觉
In the time of the Greeks, they believed that vision was somewhat analogous to the sense
触摸发生的事情是当你睁开眼睛然后看着那里的物体时
of touch. And what happened is when you open your eyes and you looked at an object there
是一些视觉火焰，一些视觉通量离开你的眼睛，走出去触摸对象
was some visual fire, some visual flux left your eye, went out and touched the object
而视觉感觉实际上是这种散发的通量和物体之间的相互作用
and the sense of vision was in fact the interaction between this emanating flux and the object
本身。这就像是一种长距离的触觉。
itself. It was like a long distance sense of touch.
随着时间的推移，对视觉工作方式的现代解释得到了发展，当然也是如此
Over time the modern interpretation of the way vision works was developed, and certainly
据我所知，到了中世纪，人们已经很清楚了。我们今天的理解方式
by the Middle Ages I think, it was quite well understood. And the way we understand today
是一个场景被光源照亮，在这种情况下是太阳。光线
is that a scene is illuminated by a light source, in this case the sun. Rays of light
落在物体上，并反映到各种不同的方向，有的
fall down onto objects and is reflected into all sorts of different directions, and some
这些光线被反射到我们的眼睛中，在那里它们聚焦在光感受器上
of those light rays are reflected into our eye, where they are focused onto photoreceptors
并导致对大脑的一些刺激，我们将其解释为视觉感知。
and lead to some stimulation to the brain, which we interpret as visual perception.